A Guide to the Melvin E. Steadman collection, 1698-1927
Library of Virginia
- Series I: Local records, 1755-1927., Extent: 10 boxes. (Box 1-10)
  - Loudoun County Unrecorded Deeds Grantor P, 1761-1888. (Box 7, Folder 14, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1232)
    Deed between Jonas Potts etc. and John Hollingsworth (1802).
    Deed between Harry Piles and Thomas Williamson (1802).
    Deed between Ann Powell and Nicholas Kile etc. (1809).
    Deed between Leven Powell and William B. Wright (1810).
    Deed between Alfred H. Powell and Richard Meadow (1811).
    Deed between William Paxson and executors of Joshua Daniel (1811).
    Deed between Burr Powell and Daniel Brown (1819).
    Deed between Timothy Pagit and Elizabeth Pagit (1824).
    Deed between Gaines Pence and William Bronaugh (1824).
    Deed between Alfred H. Powell and Stephen Rawlings (1829).
    Deed between John Leven Powell and Stephen Rawlings (1829).
    Deed between Samuel Purcell and Samuel Clendenny (1829).
    Deed between Mary and Susannah Poulston and Anne Goodin (1830).
    Deed between Peter Polen and W. H. Polen (1888).
  - Loudoun County Unrecorded Deeds Grantor R, 1772-1863. (Box 7, Folder 15, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1232)
    Deed between Sarah Rozell and James Martin (1772).
    Deed between James Ramsey and William Smith etc. (1773).
    Deed between Jacob Remey and William Lane (1779).
    Deed between James Randals and John Osburn (1779).
    Deed between Thomas Ray and Samuel Palmer (1783).
    Deed between John Robiner and Abraham Myers (1789).
    Deed between Jacob Remey and Samuel Love (1790).
    Deed between George Rust and Elizabeth Rust (1802).
    Deed between John Roler and John Steachler (1803).
    Deed between John T. Rucketts and Richard Lee (1803).
    Deed between William Redwood and Fanny Lee, executor of Thomas Ludwell Lee (1809).
    Deed between Mahlon Roach and Samuel Clendenny (1812).
    Deed between Matthew Rust and Edward Coe (1812).
    Deed between Daniel Rees and Daniel Oneal (1820).
    Deed between Stephen Rogget, Felix Triplett, and Thornton Walker (1826).
    Deed between Sampson J. Rainey and Charles F. Fadely (1863).
  - Loudoun County Unrecorded Deeds Grantor T, 1765-1816. (Box 7, Folder 16, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1232)
    Deed between John Trammell and Samuel Mobley (1765).
    Deed between Isaac Thompson and John Hunt Jr. (1787).
    Deed between Benjamin Trenary and Anthony Huffman (1792).
    Deed between William Thomas and Richard Freeman (1793).
    Deed between Israel Thompson and William Wertz (1796).
    Deed between Israel Thompson and Flemor Patteson (1808).
    Deed between Walter Taylor and Archibald Means (1807).
    Deed between James Taylor and Joseph Edwards (1816).
  - Loudoun County Unrecorded Deeds Grantor V, 1774-1859. (Box 7, Folder 17, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1233)
    Deed between Edward Vandevere and Thomas Pritchard (1774).
    Deed between Edward Vandevere and William Lane (1777).
    Deed between John Violett and Elijah Violett (1808).
    Deed between Sampson Violett and Sanford Ramey (1817).
    Deed between John Violett and Elijah Anderson (1822).
    Deed between John Violett and Elizabeth Taylor (1822).
    Deed between John Violett and Sanford Ramey (1825).
  - Loudoun County Unrecorded Deeds Grantor W, 1757-1829. (Box 7, Folder 18, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1233)
    Deed between Joseph West and Edward Tanner (1757).
    Deed between John Wheeler and Samuel Canby (1776).
    Deed between Charles White and William Said (1778).
    Deed between Thomas Winn and Amos Fox (1787).
    Deed between Joel White and John Parrott (1789).
    Deed between Lord Fairfax and Conrad Bitzer (1793).
    Deed between Thomas West and Josiah Clapham (1793).
    Deed between William Wilson and James Brown (1794).
    Deed between James Wren and Josiah Clappham (1796).
    Deed between Mary West and Lewis Ellzey (1796).
    Deed between John Wolf and Ferdinando Fairfax (1804).
    Deed between William Woody and William Bronaugh (1805).
    Deed between Peter Warner and Margaret McIlhany (1805).
    Deed between Sebastian Whoofter and Price Jacobs (1806).
    Deed between Matthew Wetherley and James Craine (1808).
    Deed between Benjamin Walker and Armistead Long and William Bronaugh (1809).
    Deed between John Wilkison and Isaac Brown (1811).
    Deed between John White and Lewis Ellzey (1812).
    Deed between Levi Wilcoxon and Richard Cockerill (1812).
    Deed between Levi Williams and Benjamin Jackson (1813).
    Deed between Martin Wildman and Joseph Wildman (1808).
    Deed between Thornton Walker and William Dorsey (1822).
    Deed between William Wilson etc. and John Pursel (1825).
    Deed between Emanuel Wallman and John Marlow (1825).
    Deed between John W. Williams and Daniel Potterfield (1829).
  - Loudoun County Unrecorded Deeds Grantor Y, 1787. (Box 7, Folder 19, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1233)
    Deed between James Young and John Dunkin (1787).
  - Loudoun County Miscellaneous bonds and receipts, 1780-1817. (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Loudoun County Election Records, 1834. (Box 8, Folder 1, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1233)
    Overseers of the Poor election.
  - Loudoun County Elector's Records, 1832. (Box 8, Folder 2, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1233)
    Charles Lewis and John Bayley election as commissioners to choose electors for President and Vice President.
  - Loudoun County Fiduciary Records, 1774-1826. (Box 8, Folder 3, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1233)
    Division of the estate of James Shedd (1774).
    Division of estate of Amos Gooden (1801)
    Division of estate of Isaac Nichols Sr. (1826)
  - Loudoun County Fiduciary Records, 1767-1849. (Box 8, Folder 4, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1233)
    Power of attorney of Samuel Hanson (1767).
    Power of attorney of T. Marshall (1791).
    Power of attorney of Tarpley Bayley (1792).
    Power of attorney of Richard Miller (1793).
    Power of attorney of Catherine Wistar (1793).
    Power of attorney of Joshua Dugan (1793).
    Power of attorney of Thomas Ellzey (1799).
    Power of attorney of Ann Powell (1809).
    Power of attorney of Edmund Jennings heirs (1839).
    Power of attorney of Catherine Waters heirs (1849).
  - Loudoun County Free Negro and Slave Records, 1827. (Box 8, Folder 5, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1233)
    Register of George Washington Sewell.
  - Loudoun County Free Negro and Slave Records, 1790-1805. (Box 8, Folder 6, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1233)
    Manumission of Millie from John Binns (1790).
    Manumission of Frank and Peter from John Wrenn (1791).
    Manumission of Jack from George Emrey (1792).
    Manumission of Sarah from George Emrey (1792).
    Manumission of Catharine from George Emrey (1792).
    Manumission of Rose and Lucy from William Hatcher (1803).
    Manumission of Molly and Susan from husband George through John A. Binns (1805).
  - Loudoun County Free Negro and Slave Records, 1824. (Box 8, Folder 7, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1233)
    Hire of Martin from executors of A.T. Mason (1825).
    Hire of Richard from Eleanor Cooksey (1839).
  - Loudoun County Free Negro and Slave Records,. (Box 8, Folder 8, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1233)
    Armistead T. Mason certificate of importation of Bill (1804).
    William B. Tyler evidence of exportation of Betty and Maria (1812).
    William B. Tyler certificate of importation of Capsy and James (1812).
    William T. Mason certificate of importation of Ellick, Milly, Eliza, Sarah, Mary, Beck, Rosina, Matilda, Jacob, and Will (1815).
    William T. Mason certificate of importation Ned, Jerry, and Ben (1816).
  - Loudoun County Grand Jury, 1759. (Box 8, Folder 9, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1233)
    Order to summon grand jury.
  - Loudoun County Indentured Servants Papers, 1784. (Box 8, Folder 10, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1233)
    Indenture of Jeremiah Murphy to Hugh Lyle.
  - Loudoun County Judgments, 1763-1802. (Box 8, Folder 11, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1233)
    Dower of Catherine Shreve Thomas (1763).
    Dower of Sarah Bishop (1797).
    Dower of Sarah Rust (1802).
  - Loudoun County Justice of the Peace Records, 1773. (Box 8, Folder 12, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1233)
    Complaint of robbery of Thomas Mason.
  - Loudoun County Land Records, 1850. (Box 8, Folder 13, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1233)
    Appointment of Asa Jackson as surveyor.
  - Loudoun County Marriage Records, 1819. (Box 8, Folder 14, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1233)
    Marriage contract of William B. Benedict and Henrietta Henderson.
  - Loudoun County Miscellaneous Records, 1871. (Box 8, Folder 15, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1233)
    Newspaper announcement of guardian for Henry and James Vanbuskirk.
  - Loudoun County Miscellaneous Records, 1786, 1841. (Box 8, Folder 16, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1233)
    Appointment of William A. Powell as notary public by John Rutherfoord.
  - Loudoun County Miscellaneous Records, 1772-1796. (Box 8, Folder 17, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1233)
    Petitions to erect water and grist mills.
  - Loudoun County Overseers of the Poor, 1813-1814. (Box 8, Folder 18, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1233)
    Appointment of Israel Lacey and David Lewis.
  - Loudoun County Plats and Surveys, 1814-1897. (Box 8, Folder 19, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1233)
    Survey of Binns land.
    Survey of Ellzey land.
    Survey of land Eliza Selden to Gasaway.
    Survey of land of Spence A. Buckner.
    Survey of land of Monroe.
    Plat of the Ridge.
  - Loudoun County Roads, 1758-1769. (Box 8, Folder 20, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1233)
    Petitions, reports, and surveys of roads and bridges.
  - Loudoun County Roads, 1770-1775. (Box 8, Folder 21, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1233)
  - Loudoun County Roads, 1782-1789. (Box 8, Folder 22, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1234)
  - Loudoun County Roads, 1790-1797. (Box 8, Folder 23, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1234)
  - Loudoun County Roads, 1801-1809. (Box 8, Folder 24, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1234)
  - Loudoun County Roads, 1810-1814. (Box 8, Folder 25, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1234)
  - Loudoun County Roads, 1824-1833. (Box 8, Folder 26, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1235)
  - Loudoun County Roads, 1874-1875. (Box 8, Folder 27, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1235)
  - Loudoun County Roads, nd. (Box 9, Folder 1, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1235)
  - Loudoun County Roads, 1781-1836. (Box 9, Folder 2, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1235)
    Appointment of road surveyors.
  - Loudoun County School Records, 1835. (Box 9, Folder 3, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1235)
    Appointment of Mortimer McIlhany as school commissioner.
  - Loudoun County Strays, 1789. (Box 9, Folder 4, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1235)
    Report of stray mares.
  - Loudoun County Tax Records, 1800, 1865. (Box 9, Folder 5, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1235)
  - Loudoun County Wills, 1758-1909. (Box 9, Folder 6, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1235)
    Will of William Shreve (1758).
    Will of John King (1784).
    Will of Joanna Lewis (1827).
    Will of Jacob Waltman (1846).
    Will of Caroline Mason (1909).
  - Madison County Deed Book U, 1851. (Box 9, Folder 7, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1235)
    Deed between Adam Hoffman and Staunton Fishback.
  - Madison County Wills, 1819. (Box 9, Folder 8, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1235)
    Will of Francis Kirtley.
  - Northumberland County County Court, 1785. (Box 9, Folder 9, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1235)
    Henry Boggess vs. William Lewis.
  - Pittsylvania County Unrecorded Deeds B, 1811. (Box 9, Folder 10, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1235)
    Deed between Joseph Baldwin and William Rawlins.
  - Prince George County Bonds, 1761. (Box 9, Folder 11, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1235)
    Bond of Leonard Marbury.
  - Prince William County Agreements, 1789-1870. (Box 9, Folder 12, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1235)
    Agreement between Nathan Triplett and William Cain (1789).
    Agreement between Ellzey family (1803)..
    Agreement between Grayson Tyler and John R. Shirley (1867-1870).
  - Prince William County Bonds, 1772-1844. (Box 9, Folder 13, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1235)
    Bond of Gabriel Baxter and Adam Mitchell (1772).
    Bond of Thomas Thornton (1774).
    Bond of Nathaniel H. Triplett (1787).
    Bond of John Luckett (1789).
    Bond of Solomon Ewell (1803).
    Bond of John Trone and Eppa Hunton (1844).
  - Prince William County, 1801-1851. (Box 9, Folder 14, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1235)
    George French vs. William Powell (1801).
    Robert Luttrell vs. Stuart and Muschett (1808).
    Henry Fairfax vs. James Deneale (1816).
    John Gibson etc. vs. Simpson and French (1824).
    Burtonsville trustees vs. Simpson etc. (1825).
    Lewis French vs. Mason French (1840).
    William French vs. Thomas J. Shaw (1840).
    Manassas Gap Railroad Co. vs. William W. Monroe (1851).
  - Prince William County County Court, 1838. (Box 9, Folder 15, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1236)
    Grand jury presentments against Isaac Florence.
  - Prince William County Chancery Court, 1833. (Box 9, Folder 16, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1236)
    Louisa C. Muschett (nee Williams) and Flora Williams vs. John W. Williams.
  - Prince William County Circuit Superior Court of Law and Chancery, 1840. (Box 9, Folder 17, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1236)
    George Atkinson vs. James and Mason French.
  - Prince William County Circuit Court, 1866-1869. (Box 9, Folder 18, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1236)
    Lovell Marders vs. Benjamin T. Chinn and Alfred Ball (1866).
    James H. McVeigh and James Chamberlain vs. William McLean (1866).
    Commonwealth vs. Robert Mason (1869).
    Commonwealth vs. Tyler (1869).
    William Muir vs. Philip D. Lipscomb executor (1869).
  - Prince William County Circuit Court, ca. 1910. (Box 9, Folder 19, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1236)
    Blank form to pay Grand Juror's fees.
  - Prince William County Recorded Deeds, 1789-1795. (Box 9, Folder 20, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1236)
    Deed between Nathaniel H. Triplett and William Carr (1789).
    Deed between Howson Hooe and Robert Cole (1795).
  - Prince William County Deed Book BB, 1813. (Box 9, Folder 21, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1236)
    Deed between Gov. James Barbour and William Shaw (1813).
  - Prince William County Deed Book C, 1737. (Box 9, Folder 22, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1236)
    Deed between John Harll and William Harll.
  - Prince William County Deed Book #17, 1841-1842. (Box 9, Folder 23, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1236)
    Deed between John Trone and Joseph Thompson estate (1841).
    Deed between John Fontaine and Washington Norvell (1842).
  - Prince William County Deed Book #19, 1844-1847. (Box 9, Folder 24, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1236)
    Deed between Phillip Carter and William Carter (1844).
    Deed between Thomas R. Love and John Graham (1845).
    Deed between William A. Carter etc. and Alfred Ball (1845).
    Deed between Stephen French etc. and Allen Harrison (1845).
    Deed between B.E. Harrison and George Carter (1845).
    Deed between Eppa Hunton and Elijah Petty (1846).
    Deed between John Delaplane etc. and Charles H. Hunton (1846).
    Deed between Jesse Ewell and Alfred Ball etc. (1847).
    Deed between Layton Hansburger and Thomas J. French (1847).
    Deed between William Sexsmith and Aylett Nicol (1847).
    Deed between Isaac Lee and Thomas A. Clark (1847).
  - Prince William County Deed Book #21, 1837-1851. (Box 9, Folder 25, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1236)
    Deed between Edward King and Orange and Alexandria Railroad Co. (1849).
    Deed between William French and Thomas Weir (1837).
    Deed between James Stewart and Orange and Alexandria Railroad Co. (1850).
    Deed between William Weir and Orange and Alexandria Railroad Co. (1850).
    Deed between James K. Kinton and John Tyler (1851).
  - Prince William County Deed Book #25, 1860. (Box 9, Folder 26, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1236)
    Deed between William Musser and William Tayloe etc.
  - Prince William County Deed Book #27, 1868. (Box 9, Folder 27, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1236)
    Deed between James Herrell and Luther Lynn.
  - Prince William County Deed Book #35, 1884-1885. (Box 9, Folder 28, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1236)
    Deed between Henry P. Rogers and Richard Hauley etc. (1884).
    Deed between Walter Rogers etc. and Peter Poland etc. (1885).
  - Prince William County Deed Book #38, 1888. (Box 9, Folder 29, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1236)
    Deed between Westwood Hutchinson and Peter Poland.
  - Prince William County Unrecorded Deeds B, 1790. (Box 9, Folder 30, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1236)
    Deed between Cuthbert Babbitt and Nathaniel Wickleff.
  - Prince William County Unrecorded Deeds C, 1750. (Box 9, Folder 31, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1236)
    Deed between Isaac Foster and Charles Carter.
  - Prince William County Unrecorded Deeds H, 1737. (Box 9, Folder 32, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1236)
  - Prince William County Unrecorded Deeds L, 1789. (Box 9, Folder 33, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1236)
    Deed between John B. Luckett and William Carr.
  - Prince William County Unrecorded Deeds R, 1775, 1831. (Box 9, Folder 34, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1236)
    Deed between Benjamin Rector and Anne White (1775).
    Deed between William Reide and Mordeon Sinclair (1831).
  - Prince William County Unrecorded Deeds T, 1763. (Box 9, Folder 35, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1236)
    Deed between John Taylor etc. and John Donnman.
  - Prince William County Unrecorded Deeds W, 1810-1854. (Box 9, Folder 36, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1236)
    Deed between Robert Ware and Peter Davis (1810).
    Deed between Humphrey Walker and Temple Walker (1819).
    Deed between Baylor Walker and Temple Walker (1822).
    Deed between John Walker vs. John Defarges (1854).
  - Prince William County Fiduciary Records, 1841. (Box 9, Folder 37, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1236)
    Power of attorney of John Anderson.
  - Prince William County Miscellaneous, 1876. (Box 9, Folder 38, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1236)
    Petition against allowing a liquor license in town.
  - Prince William County Miscellaneous, 1874. (Box 9, Folder 39, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1236)
    List of persons assessed a tax on dogs.
  - Prince William County Plats and Surveys, 1743-1865. (Box 9, Folder 40, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1236)
    Plat of Charles Ewell land (1743).
    Survey of lots leased on Bristoe Tract (1824).
    Survey of William Thomas Nelson (1835).
    Survey of lands of John Tyler (1865).
  - Prince William County Reconstruction, 1865-1871. (Box 9, Folder 41, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1236)
    Statement from the Provost Marshall disallowing citizens who held office under the Confederate government to hold office until they take the amnesty oath (1865).
    Claim of Margaret Robinson (1871).
  - Prince William County Road and Bridge Records, nd. (Box 9, Folder 42, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1236)
    Receipt.
  - Prince William County Road and Bridge Records, 1825-1826. (Box 9, Folder 43, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1236)
    Cedar Run Bridge records including drawings, receipts, and agreements.
  - Prince William County School Records, 1847-1851. (Box 9, Folder 44, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1236)
    Papers regarding school districts.
  - Prince William County Levy Papers, 1765. (Box 9, Folder 44a-c, Reel [Not filmed])
    Levy papers and tithe list.
  - Prince William County Wills, 1763-1848. (Box 9, Folder 45, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1236)
    Will of Easterlay Cocke (1763).
    Will of William Graham (1821).
    Will of John Lee (1848).
  - Richmond Chancery District Court, 1816-1826. (Box 10, Folder 1, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1236)
    Silas Wherry vs. John A. Binns (1816).
    Thomas Lacy executors vs. John Binns executors (1826).
  - Rockingham County Circuit Superior Court of Law and Chancery, 1850. (Box 10, Folder 2, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1236)
    John R. Plecker and S. Effinger vs. Peachy Harrison etc.
  - Stafford County Unrecorded Deeds H, 1833-1853. (Box 10, Folder 3, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1236)
    Survey for Sarah Harrison (1833).
    Survey for John Washington (1853).
  - Stafford County Plats and Surveys, 1812. (Box 10, Folder 4, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1236)
    Survey for Thomas Ford's land.
    Survey for John England.
    Survey for Thomas Dallas.
  - Stafford County Wills, 1698-1720. (Box 10, Folder 5, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1236)
    Will of Thomas Ellzey (1698 and 1719).
  - Westmoreland County Recorded Deeds, 1786. (Box 10, Folder 6, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1236)
    Deed between Mordecai Cooke and George Payne.
  - Westmoreland County Plats and Surveys, 1728. (Box 10, Folder 7, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1236)
    Survey for John and William Elliot.
  - Westmoreland County Free Negro and Slave Records, 1756. (Box 10, Folder 8, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1236)
    Board charges for work on Mattox Church sent to William Coaghill.
  - Virginia First Military District Records, 1869. (Box 10, Folder 9, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1236)
    Circular letter regarding Spotswood Childress vs. James Nokes.
  - Virginia General Assembly, 1806. (Box 10, Folder 10, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1236)
    Petition from the Bishops and Conference of the Methoidst Episcopal Church in Norfolk, to ban liquor from public worship.
  - Virginia, Miscellaneous Courts [unspecified], 1750, 1823. (Box 10, Folder 11, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1236)
    Hamilton vs. Lynhard (nd).
    Lord Fairfax vs. Nicholas Seward (nd).
    Benjamin Grayson vs. William Barkley (1750).
    John Turner vs. Uriah McKnight (1823).
  - Virginia, Miscellaneous Deeds, 1895. (Box 10, Folder 12, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1236)
    Deed between L. S. Gordon and Charles A. Newton.
  - Virginia Miscellaneous Free Negro and Slave Records, 1765. (Box 10, Folder 13, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1236)
    Board charges.
  - Virginia Miscellaneous Free Negro and Slave Records, nd. (Box 10, Folder 14, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1236)
    Slave hires [?].
  - Virginia Miscellaneous Free Negro and Slave Records, 1809-1811. (Box 10, Folder 15, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1236)
    Slave sales receipts.
  - Virginia, Miscellaneous Indentures, 1790. (Box 10, Folder 16, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1236)
    Indenture of Hannah Burchett to Jonah Nixon.
  - Virginia, Miscellaneous, 1755. (Box 10, Folder 17, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1236)
    Advertisement and poems.
  - Virginia, Miscellaneous Plats and Surveys, 1791-1824. (Box 10, Folder 18, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1236)
  - Virginia, Miscellaneous Railroads, 1854. (Box 10, Folder 19, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1236)
    Plan of the Manassas Gap Railroad Company through the land of John Graham.
  - Virginia, Miscellaneous Wills, 1805. (Box 10, Folder 20, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1236)
    Accounts on the estate of John Williams (1816).
    List of the heirs of Thomas Champe (1835).
  - Miscellaneous Wrappers, nd. (Box 10, Folder 21, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1236)
  - Fragments, 1799-1848. (Box 10, Folder 22, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1236)
  - California, San Bernardino Bonds, 1883. (Box 10, Folder 23, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1237)
    Promissory note to Edmund Flagg.
  - Kentucky, Henderson County Deeds, 1843-1852. (Box 10, Folder 24, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1237)
    Deed between John Hancock and Henderson Hancock (1843).
    Deed between Harrison Graves and Alexander B. Barret (1852).
  - Kentucky, Henderson County Fiduciary Records, 1827-1838. (Box 10, Folder 25, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1237)
    Power of attorney of John Hancock (1827).
    Power of attorney of Mary S. Gwatkin (1838).
  - Kentucky, Henderson County Marriage Records, 1816. (Box 10, Folder 26, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1237)
    Marriage contract of Edward Chatham and Jemimia Hancock.
  - Kentucky, Henderson County Oaths, 1819. (Box 10, Folder 27, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1237)
    Oath regarding slaves.
  - Kentucky, Lexington Fiduciary Records, 1816. (Box 10, Folder 28, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1237)
    Power of attorney of Mary Mason.
    Power of attorney of Leven Luckett, William Hale, Townsend Peyton, as devisees of Francis Peyton.